<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://Han-Yindan.github.io</id>
    <title>hyd&apos;s Web</title>
    <updated>2021-05-12T01:19:25.595Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://Han-Yindan.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://Han-Yindan.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>The wrong time to learn how to do something is when you need to do it, but in truth most people only learn how to do something when it is necessary.</subtitle>
    <logo>https://Han-Yindan.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://Han-Yindan.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2021, hyd&apos;s Web</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于我]]></title>
        <id>https://Han-Yindan.github.io/post/guan-yu-wo/</id>
        <link href="https://Han-Yindan.github.io/post/guan-yu-wo/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-05-10T01:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Follow me on：https://github.com/insjfsafh</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[networking]]></title>
        <id>https://Han-Yindan.github.io/post/networking/</id>
        <link href="https://Han-Yindan.github.io/post/networking/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-05-10T01:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In the morning, I learned entity relationships in database, and this is the seventh champter.That a manner to help you to set up a module between two or more relationships. I mean although you may know some tables and the data of it, some of them have the relationships among each other. If you have no official methods or general methods to detect them, you may be confused to set up some keys like foreign keys, maybe there still exists some reasons.<br>
In the afternoon, I learned that full-adder can be constructed circut from two half-adder. And two of four bits of binary can be added by full-added but then add 0110, in order to convert to BCD. It's a regular formula you can find by yourself through their truth tables, and you will find two of four bits of binary added compares with BCD are just different over 9 number.(01001)--&gt;binary(01001)--&gt;BCD<br>
10 number(01010)-&gt;binary(10000)--&gt;BCD<br>
below are the knowledge I learned in the evening.<br>
DNS 看这个就懂<br>
一篇blog 带你general underestanding 计算机网络<br>
IP 和 MAC 都是必要的<br>
today I know the network card is equal to network adapter.<br>
you must have it and then you can connect to the WIFI, but is there have virtual or physics?<br>
image.png</p>
<p>I don't know the vmawre is actually from my visual system? if it is why I have only two<br>
and is the function of local connection is to connect to another computer with ??what the necessity of it?</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[git]]></title>
        <id>https://Han-Yindan.github.io/post/git/</id>
        <link href="https://Han-Yindan.github.io/post/git/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-05-10T01:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>https://www.cnblogs.com/liaow...<br>
git's code color<br>
maven in idea<br>
detail teaching in setting.xml<br>
https://www.cnblogs.com/hongm...<br>
location of setting<br>
https://blog.csdn.net/fengqin...<br>
add mirror if you have no vpn<br>
https://blog.csdn.net/weixin_...<br>
I am almost crazy when I have set my setting.xml, but still have red lines in plugin, this may be helpful:<br>
https://blog.csdn.net/weixin_...<br>
https://www.freesion.com/arti...<br>
https://www.cnblogs.com/evach...</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I begin my English diary for not only IETLES in July,2021, but also for technique and to memorize everyday detail.]]></title>
        <id>https://Han-Yindan.github.io/post/hello-gridea/</id>
        <link href="https://Han-Yindan.github.io/post/hello-gridea/">
        </link>
        <updated>2018-12-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>《Git在IDEA中的使用（详细图文全解）》https://blog.csdn.net/mucaoyx/article/details/98476174?utm_source=app&amp;app_version=4.6.0<br>
this can help you learn the basic operation of the git.<br>
but I still not know how to roll back when I have push it to the github.<br>
I still have limitied knowlege of github.<br>
especially copy(admire) others beauty code.<br>
I communicated with an excellent classmate, learning that before relying others people, making yourself better enough.<br>
I known that every class is interesting and useful which I taken this semester. but maybe the not every minutes<br>
support my idea of tomcat -- a web server, but not done marven, which is needed in springboot, which means you needn't configure environment varible<br>
-java learning:<br>
define of array ,two way<br>
exception which needed to included(must), but some exception in java can be selected<br>
I know package ,class is the directory, but why use this way?<br>
supper():used in child in order invoke father's class or variable,but ....<br>
--SQL:<br>
not exists<br>
attribute in(x,y,z,...)（QA4 I change some answers given by teacher,and I think also can be done by union, but too much hassle）<br>
--tool class:<br>
roost is becoming popular!almost in 10?<br>
c is the most popular, if you want initiate in hardware?<br>
java is the second</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>